<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GigAdvisor</string>
    <string name="Avanti">Prosegui</string>
    <string name="Name">Nome</string>
    <string name="Surname">Cognome</string>
    <string name="Email">Email</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="prompt_password"></string>
    <string name="repeat_password">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >4 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="title_activity_platform">PlatformActivity</string>
    <string name="platforms">PLATFORMS</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="amazon">AMAZON</string>
    <string name="foodora">FOODORA</string>
    <string name="justeat">JUST EAT</string>
    <string name="deliveroo">DELIVEROO</string>
    <string name="uber">UBER</string>
    <string name="upwork">UP WORK</string>
    <string name="crowdsourcing">crowdsourcing</string>
    <string name="food_delivery">food delivery</string>
    <string name="transport_service">transport-service</string>
    <string name="micro_tasking">micro-tasking</string>
    <string name="Amazon_Mechanical_Turk">Amazon Mechanical Turk</string>
    <string name="Foodora">Foodora</string>
    <string name="Just_Eat">Just Eat</string>
    <string name="Deliveroo">Deliveroo</string>
    <string name="Uber">Uber</string>
    <string name="UpWork">Up Work</string>
    <string name="RegistrationActivity">REGISTRATION</string>
    <string name="Platforms">Platforms</string>
    <string name="Rate">Rate your gig</string>
    <string name="rate_amazon">Rate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dacancellare">Dacancellare</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <string name="Presentation">GigAdvisor: a tool to...</string>
    <string name="about">GigAdvisor in a nutshell...</string>
    <string name="scritta1">An interdisciplinary research</string>
    <string name="disciplina">GigAdvisor is an experimental platform designed to work within the scenario of digital labor platforms, a phenomenon marked by a variety of issues - low levels of social protection for gig-workers; pervasive algorithmic control;
        tomization of work processes, etc. - that increase the need for more insightful empirical investigations and effective regulatory solutions.
        The platform allows crowdworkers to express, share and discuss different kinds of assessments (by means of predefined scales and free text)
        on the quality of their experiences with the platforms they work for.
        Resulting from a research project that brings together labor studies and data-driven computational social science (CSS), the
        initiative is an attempt to explore new approaches to the analysis and regulation of digital economy.</string>

    <string name="scritta2">The goals</string>
    <string name="goal">The first goal is to gather data to be used in CSS research on gig economy.\n
        Data collected through users’ interaction with the tool - enriched with geographical and temporal metatags - will not
        only be made available to the workers thanks to real-time visualizations, but also exploited for research purposes.
        Social network analysis, sentiment analysis and other CSS methods can be precious to answer questions of both normative and empirical nature:
            <item>assess the impact of legislative policies</item>
            <item>support ​(temporally and spatially) ​fine-grained investigation about working conditions</item>
            <item>identify patterns in the behavior of market operators (e.g. unfair practices)</item>
        <i>Regulatory design</i>
        Drawing from the “techno-regulation” paradigm - the idea of influencing individuals by building norms
        or nudge strategies into technological devices (Leenes 2013) - a second goal is to start fiddling with the design of solutions
        allowing to exploit the regulatory effects that can be induced by tools allowing to build up a reputational image of labor platforms.
        Special attention will be paid, in this vein, to figure out new ways to leverage the power of analytics and visualization to increase
        the conditioning power of a “data-enhanced” reputation.</string>

    <string name="safetyatwork">La sicurezza sul lavoro in Italia è normata dal DLgs. 81/08 o Testo Unico sulla Sicurezza sul Lavoro.
        La legge stabilisce regole, procedure e misure preventive da adottare per rendere più sicuri i luoghi di lavoro, quali essi siano.
        L’obiettivo è quello di evitare o comunque ridurre al minimo l’esposizione dei lavoratori a rischi legati all’attività lavorativa per evitare infortuni o incidenti o, peggio,
        contrarre una malattia professionale.La sicurezza sul lavoro è a carico del datore di lavoro, dipendenti o collaboratori che
        devono comunque adottare un comportamento consono alla struttura in cui si trovano o alla mansione loro affidata.</string>

    <string name="scritta3">Platform\'s modules</string>
    <string name="module">The tool, still under development, currently encompasses three components:

        <b>"Rate your gig"</b>
        The module allows crowdworkers to evaluate digital labor platforms they work for, according to a series of predefined criteria
        (e.g. employer fairness, payment timeliness) mapping most relevant

        <b>"See platform's rating"</b>
        The module offers the real-time analysis and visualization of data resulting from the assessments made by crowd workers using the
        “RATE YOUR GIG!”

        <b>"Connect with others"</b>
        A forum allowing crowd workers to discuss issues and share ideas about their working experience.</string>

    <string name="scritta4">Next steps</string>
    <string name="nextstep">We are planning to use GigAdvisor within experimental settings involving real workers and designed
        in collaboration with unions and gig-workers associations. If you are interested, feel free to contact us.</string>

    <string name="pubb1">
        Lettieri, Nicola, et al. Platform Economy and Techno-Regulation—Experimenting with Reputation and Nudge. Future Internet, 2019, 11.7: 163.
    </string>

    <string name="pubb2">
        De Minicis, M., Donà, S., Lettieri, N., &amp; Marocco, M. (2019).
        Disciplina e tutela del lavoro nelle digital labour platform. Un modello di tecno-regolazione.
    </string>

    <string name="pubb3">
        Lettieri N., Digital Labour platforms, algorithmic governance and techno-regulation: towards the
        computational evolution of law and labor studies.
        Talk presented at the "Reshaping Work 2019" International Conference - Amsterdam - 24 October 2019
    </string>

    <string name="initialMessage">This is a prototype of an experimental mobile-application under development for pure research purposes.
    Data presented in following pages are fictitious.</string>
    <string name="link">https://gigadvisor.herokuapp.com/GigAdvisor/login/</string>

    <string name="nicola">
        Researcher at INAPP, Rome. Adjunct professor of Legal informatics at the University of Sannio
    </string>

    <string name="malandrino">
        Associate professor at the Department of Computer Science of the University of
        Salerno, member of ISISLab
    </string>

    <string name="rocco">
        Research fellow and adjunct professor at Department of Computer Science of the University of Salerno
    </string>

    <string name="alfonso">
        Research fellow at the Department of Computer Science of the University of Salerno and member of ISISLab
    </string>

    <string name="carmine">
        Bachelor\'s Degree in Computer Science \n at the University of Salerno
    </string>

    <string-array name="region_item">
        <item>Abruzzo</item>
        <item>Basilicata</item>
        <item>Calabria</item>
        <item>Campania</item>
        <item>Emilia Romagna</item>
        <item>Friuli Venezia Giulia</item>
        <item>Lazio</item>
        <item>Liguria</item>
        <item>Lombardia</item>
        <item>Marche</item>
        <item>Molise</item>
        <item>Piemonte</item>
        <item>Puglia</item>
        <item>Sardegna</item>
        <item>Sicilia</item>
        <item>Toscana</item>
        <item>Umbria</item>
        <item>Valle Aosta</item>
        <item>Veneto</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_sex">
        <item>Maschio</item>
        <item>Femmina</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="alertMessage">I dati inseriti in questo form di recensione verranno utilizzati per
    scopi puramente di ricerca. Tutto ciò che viene espresso è visualizzato in forma assolutamente anonima.
    I dati non verranno mostrati in nessun modo.</string>

    <string name="platformMessage">This module allows crowd workers to evaluate digital labour platforms they work for, according to a series of predefined criteria</string>

    <string name="graphmessage">This module shows real-time analysis\nand visualization
    of data resulting from the assessments made by crowd workers.</string>

    <string name="teamdescription">The project stems from an ongoing interdisciplinary collaboration involving
        researchers with a background in legal informatics, computer science, labor law, economic sociology.
    </string>

    <string name="manuel">Researcher at INAPP. Head of the research group <i>\"Technological innovation, industrial relations and labor market\"</i> </string>

    <string name="massimo">Researcher at INAPP. Member of the research group <i>\"Technological innovation, industrial relations and labor market\"</i></string>

    <string name="silvia">Researcher fellow at INAPP. Member of the research group <i>\"Technological innovation, industrial relations and labor market\"</i></string>

    <string name="publication1">Lettieri, Nicola, et al. Platform Economy and Techno-Regulation—Experimenting with Reputation and Nudge. Future Internet, 2019, 11.7: 163.</string>

    <string name="publication2">De Minicis, M., Donà, S., Lettieri, N., &amp; Marocco, M. (2019). Disciplina e tutela del lavoro nelle digital labour platform. Un modello di tecno-regolazione.</string>

    <string name="publication3">Lettieri N., Digital Labour platforms, algorithmic governance and techno-regulation: towards the computational evolution of law and labor studies. Talk presented at the "Reshaping Work 2019" International Conference - Amsterdam - 24 October 2019</string>

    <string name="gigadvisorinanutshell">
GigAdvisor is an experimental app for data driven exploration of platform economy. Designed for gigworkers, researchers and citizens, the tool implements the following pipeline:</string>

    <string name="messagelogin">To assess the platform you have been working form please register/login.</string>
    <string name="dialoglogin">LOGIN NEEDED</string>

    <string name="messagedownload">To download raw data stored on GigAdvisor, please login.</string>
</resources>
